phpbbplanet.com 2012-06-12

# phpbbplanet.com * reliable phpbb hosting / webhosting with great network & dedicated server uptime

**Information**

When you sign up for our service, we will ask you to provide contact information such as email address. 

We may ask you to complete user surveys, and to provide certain demographic information, such as age, gender, special interests, etc. You do not have to provide this type of information to use our service if you do not want to. 

If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you for information about your operating system, software and other technical matters. 

When you visit our Web site we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the pages on our Web site that you view. We may tie this information to the personally identifiable information we have about you. 

We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as a repeat visitor or a customer when you visit our Web site. See "What is a Cookie" below. We may tie this cookie to the personally identifiable information we have about you. 

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

We will use your personally identifiable information only as follows: 

· To announce special offers or provide other information from time to time via e-mail. We may also send e-mail announcing special offers by our third parties, but we will not provide the third parties with your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. 

· To improve our service and the marketing of our service. For example, we may use the information we gather from user surveys, demographic data, and web site visits to help us improve or target our Web site and customize your visit. 

We will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to any other person other than: 

· a law enforcement or regulatory agency at their request; 

· a person or company who acquires our business; 

· third parties who perform services on our behalf (such as payment processing), subject to the third party agreeing with us that it will keep your personally identifiable information confidential; 

· To our subsidiaries and affiliates; or 

· As otherwise needed to protect or enforce or rights or the rights of others. 

We absolutely do not transfer or sell your information for inclusion on third party e-mail or other marketing lists. 

**Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may share aggregate statistical data about our customers with third parties, such as advertisers or suppliers. This aggregate statistical data will not identify you personally. 

**What is a Cookie**

A "cookie" is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our web site so that we may customize your visit. 

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 

. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Security of Your Information**

We store your personally identifiable information. 

**Children's Privacy**

Our service is not available to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.
